<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FortuneTeller</string>
    <string name="title">Fortune Teller</string>
    <string name="description">Using a combination of Big Data, AR, VR, AI, and if-statements, Fortune Teller predicts your future with 99.99% accuracy.</string>
    <string name="accept_quiz">I want to be on the cutting edge of my future</string>
    <string name="reject_quiz">I\'m kind of busy...</string>
    <string name="quiz_directions">Please answer a few questions to help our fortune teller better predict your future.</string>
    <string name="question1_name">Name</string>
    <string name="question2_email">Email address</string>
    <string name="question3_">Question #3</string>
    <string name="question4_meeting_attendance">How many MDC meeting are you planning on attending this Fall?</string>
    <string name="end_quiz">Tell My Fortune!</string>
    <string name="low_meeting_count_label">Hmm...not the best fortune I\'ve ever seen...  You can always add more meetings and peer into the crystal ball again! </string>
    <string name="medium_meeting_count_label">Your future is bright!  But there is still more that MDC can do for you...</string>
    <string name="high_meeting_count_label">Your future is beautiful and fulfilling.  My work is done.</string>
    <string name="add_another_meeting">Add another MDC meeting!</string>
    <string name="email_button">Sign me up!</string>
    <string-array name="bad_fortunes">
        <item>Willie the Wildcat is personally disappointed in you.</item>
        <item>You forget how to do the Wabash.</item>
        <item>You wear an itchy sweater every day for the rest of your life, to be worn with no undershirt at all times.</item>
        <item>Every time you wear ear buds they are violently yanked out of your ears.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="okay_fortunes">
        <item>You become a junior sales associate at a midrange paper supply firm.  That'll show em.</item>
        <item>Okay fortune 2</item>
        <item>Okay fortune 3</item>
        <item>Okay fortune 4</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="good_fortunes">
        <item>Good fortune 1</item>
        <item>You marry your soul mate that you met at MDC.</item>
        <item>Bill Snyder asks you for your autograph.</item>
        <item>You achieve the highest honor possible as successor to the MDC president.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="meetingCountOptions">
        <item>What\'s MDC???</item>
        <item>Hmm...I might try a few meetings...</item>
        <item>You guys are basically my family already!</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
